<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Xtreme Bucket List</string>
    <string name="gcm_sender_id">id:942771046607</string>
    <string name="facebook_app_id">171437900223755</string>
    <string name="file_provider_authority" translatable="false">com.brainyapps.xtremebucketlist.fileprovider</string>

    <string name="crash_toast_text">We\'re sorry but Xtreme Bucket List\' unexpectedly crashed. Please let us know and fix this error by sending this report to us.</string>
    <string name="CANCEL">CANCEL</string>
    <string name="CLOSE">CLOSE</string>
    <string name="Error">Error</string>
    <string name="CONFIRM">CONFIRM</string>
    <string name="profile_photo">Profile Photo</string>
    <string name="NA">N/A</string>
    <string name="NO">NO</string>
    <string name="OK">OK</string>
    <string name="Okay">Okay</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="Success">Success</string>
    <string name="Warning">Warning</string>
    <string name="YES">YES</string>
    <string name="try_again">TRY AGAIN</string>
    <string name="sign_up_title">SIGN UP</string>
    <string name="forgot_password">Forgot Password?</string>
    <string name="signup_here"><b>Sign up HERE!</b></string>

    <string name="want_exit">Are you sure you want to exit?</string>
    <string name="msg_error_network">Oops! Please connect to the internet and try again.</string>
    <string name="and">%1$s and %2$s</string>
    <string name="msg_error_permission">Check your permissions in Settings -> Apps -> Xtreme Bucket List -> Permissions</string>
    <string name="msg_error_permission_storage">Check your storage permissions in Settings -> Apps -> Xtreme Bucket List -> Permissions</string>
    <string name="msg_error_permission_camera">Check your camera permissions in Settings -> Apps -> Xtreme Bucket List -> Permissions</string>
    <string name="upload_photo">Upload photo</string>
    <string name="select_gallery">Select from gallery</string>
    <string name="take_new_photo">Take a new photo</string>
    <string name="valid_confirm_avatar">Are you sure you want to proceed without a profile photo?</string>
    <string name="valid_Invalid_other">We detected an error. Help me review your answer and try again.</string>
    <string name="banned_lable">Sorry, you are banned.</string>
    <string name="invalid_incorrect_password">Password entered is incorrect.</string>
    <string name="invalid_social_login">Error encountered during authentication. Please try again.</string>
    <string name="valid_No_email">Please enter your email.</string>
    <string name="valid_Invalid_email">Email address is invalid.</string>
    <string name="success_forgot_password">Success! We’ve sent a password reset link to your email.</string>
    <string name="msg_notification_accepted">%1$s commented on your post.</string>
    <string name="msg_notification_declined">%1$s accepted your connection request.</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="terms_conditions">Terms and Conditions</string>
    <string name="report_problem">Report a Problem</string>
    <string name="about_app">About the App</string>
    <string name="email_not_registered_create_account">Email entered is not registered. Create an account now?</string>

    <string name="onboarding_first_text">It\'s the perfect time  to live out your bucked list.</string>
    <string name="onboarding_second_text">To accomplish your  dreams,start now  and make it happen during your lifetime</string>
    <string name="onboarding_third_text">List all your things  you want to do and track  your archivements</string>

    <string name="gps_network_not_enabled">Location service not enabled</string>
    <string name="gps_network_enable_message">Your location service is turn off. Please turn on it.</string>
    <string name="success_fingerprint">Success! Your fingerprint can be used for unlocking the app.</string>

    <string name="no_support_fingerprint">Your device doesn\'t support fingerprint authentication</string>
    <string name="no_finger_permission">Please enable the fingerprint permission</string>
    <string name="no_fingerprint_configured">No fingerprint configured. Please register at least one fingerprint in your device\'s Settings</string>
    <string name="disable_lockscreen">Please enable lockscreen security in your device\'s Settings</string>
    <string name="finger_authentication_failed">Fingerprint authentication failed.</string>

    <string name="about">"
         <![CDATA[
        <p>This app was created to fill a void I noticed when I tried to find a way to create a timeline and the necessary resources needed to fulfill meaningful activities and ideas.</p>
        <p>A place to not only create a dream board but realize the accomplishment of said goals.</p>
        ]]>
    "</string>
    <string name="privacy">"
        <![CDATA[
<h2>Definitions</h2>
<h3>Personal Data</h3>
<p>Personal Data means data about a living individual who can be identified from those data (or from those and other information either in our possession or likely to come into our possession).</p>
<h3>Usage Data</h3>
<p>Usage Data is data collected automatically either generated by the use of the Service or from the Service infrastructure itself (for example, the duration of a page visit).</p>
<h3>Cookies</h3>
<p>Cookies are small pieces of data stored on a User’s device.</p>
<h3>Data Controller</h3>
<p>Data Controller means a person who (either alone or jointly or in common with other persons) determines the purposes for which and the manner in which any personal data are, or are to be, processed.</p>
<p>For the purpose of this Privacy Policy, we are a Data Controller of your data.</p>
<h3>Data Processor (or Service Providers)</h3>
<p>Data Processor (or Service Provider) means any person (other than an employee of the Data Controller) who processes the data on behalf of the Data Controller.</p>
<p>We may use the services of various Service Providers in order to process your data more effectively.</p>
<h3>Data Subject</h3>
<p>Data Subject is any living individual who is the subject of Personal Data.</p>
<h3>User</h3>
<p>The User is the individual using our Service. The User corresponds to the Data Subject, who is the subject of Personal Data.</p>
<h3>Information Collection And Use</h3>
<p>We collect several different types of information for various purposes to provide and improve our Service to you.</p>
<h3>Types of Data Collected</h3>
<h3>Personal Data</h3>
<p>While using our Service, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you ("Personal Data"). Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to:</p>
<p>•	Email address</p>
<p>•	First name and last name</p>
<p>•	Phone number</p>
<p>•	Address, State, Province, ZIP/Postal code, City</p>
<p>•	Cookies and Usage Data</p>
<h3>Usage Data</h3>
<p>We may also collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Service or when you access the Service by or through a mobile device ("Usage Data").</p>
<p>This Usage Data may include information such as your computer's Internet Protocol address (e.g. IP address), browser type, browser version, the pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages, unique device identifiers and other diagnostic data.</p>
<p>When you access the Service by or through a mobile device, this Usage Data may include information such as the type of mobile device you use, your mobile device unique ID, the IP address of your mobile device, your mobile operating system, the type of mobile Internet browser you use, unique device identifiers and other diagnostic data.</p>
<h3>Location Data</h3>
<p>We may use and store information about your location if you give us permission to do so (“Location Data”). We use this data to provide features of our Service, to improve and customize our Service.</p>
<p>You can enable or disable location services when you use our Service at any time, through your device settings.</p>
<h3>Tracking Cookies Data</h3>
<p>We use cookies and similar tracking technologies to track the activity on our Service and hold certain information.</p>
<p>Cookies are files with small amount of data which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a website and stored on your device. Tracking technologies also used are beacons, tags, and scripts to collect and track information and to improve and analyze our Service.</p>
<p>You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Service.</p>
<p>Examples of Cookies we use:</p>
<p>•	Session Cookies. We use Session Cookies to operate our Service.</p>
<p>•	Preference Cookies. We use Preference Cookies to remember your preferences and various settings.</p>
<p>•	Security Cookies. We use Security Cookies for security purposes.</p>
<h3>Use of Data</h3>
<p>Xtreme Bucket List uses the collected data for various purposes:</p>
<p>•	To provide and maintain our Service</p>
<p>•	To notify you about changes to our Service</p>
<p>•	To allow you to participate in interactive features of our Service when you choose to do so</p>
<p>•	To provide customer support</p>
<p>•	To gather analysis or valuable information so that we can improve our Service</p>
<p>•	To monitor the usage of our Service</p>
<p>•	To detect, prevent and address technical issues</p>
<h3>Retention of Data</p>
<p>Xtreme Bucket List will retain your Personal Data only for as long as is necessary for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy. We will retain and use your Personal Data to the extent necessary to comply with our legal obligations (for example, if we are required to retain your data to comply with applicable laws), resolve disputes, and enforce our legal agreements and policies.</p>
<p>Xtreme Bucket List will also retain Usage Data for internal analysis purposes. Usage Data is generally retained for a shorter period of time, except when this data is used to strengthen the security or to improve the functionality of our Service, or we are legally obligated to retain this data for longer time periods.</p>
<h3>Transfer Of Data</h3>
<p>Your information, including Personal Data, may be transferred to — and maintained on — computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection laws may differ than those from your jurisdiction.</p>
<p>If you are located outside United States and choose to provide information to us, please note that we transfer the data, including Personal Data, to United States and process it there.</p>
<p>Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.</p>
<p>Xtreme Bucket List will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy and no transfer of your Personal Data will take place to an organization or a country unless there are adequate controls in place including the security of your data and other personal information.</p>
<h2>Disclosure Of Data</h2>
<h3>Business Transaction</h3>
<p>If Xtreme Bucket List is involved in a merger, acquisition or asset sale, your Personal Data may be transferred. We will provide notice before your Personal Data is transferred and becomes subject to a different Privacy Policy.</p>
<h3>Disclosure for Law Enforcement</h3>
<p>Under certain circumstances, Xtreme Bucket List may be required to disclose your Personal Data if required to do so by law or in response to valid requests by public authorities (e.g. a court or a government agency).</p>
<h3>Legal Requirements</h3>
<p>Xtreme Bucket List may disclose your Personal Data in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to:</p>
<p>•	To comply with a legal obligation</p>
<p>•	To protect and defend the rights or property of Xtreme Bucket List</p>
<p>•	To prevent or investigate possible wrongdoing in connection with the Service</p>
<p>•	To protect the personal safety of users of the Service or the public</p>
<p>•	To protect against legal liability</p>
<h3>Security Of Data</h3>
<p>The security of your data is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Data, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.</p>
<h3>"Do Not Track" Signals</h3>
<p>We do not support Do Not Track ("DNT"). Do Not Track is a preference you can set in your web browser to inform websites that you do not want to be tracked.</p>
<p>You can enable or disable Do Not Track by visiting the Preferences or Settings page of your web browser.</p>
<h3>Your Rights</h3>
<p>Xtreme Bucket List aims to take reasonable steps to allow you to correct, amend, delete, or limit the use of your Personal Data.</p>
<p>Whenever made possible, you can update your Personal Data directly within your account settings section. If you are unable to change your Personal Data, please contact us to make the required changes.</p>
<p>If you wish to be informed what Personal Data we hold about you and if you want it to be removed from our systems, please contact us.</p>
<p>In certain circumstances, you have the right:</p>
<p>•	To access and receive a copy of the Personal Data we hold about you</p>
<p>•	To rectify any Personal Data held about you that is inaccurate</p>
<p>•	To request the deletion of Personal Data held about you</p>
<p>You have the right to data portability for the information you provide to Xtreme Bucket List. You can request to obtain a copy of your Personal Data in a commonly used electronic format so that you can manage and move it.</p>
<p>Please note that we may ask you to verify your identity before responding to such requests.</p>
<h3>Service Providers</h3>
<p>We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service ("Service Providers"), to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform Service-related services or to assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.</p>
<p>These third parties have access to your Personal Data only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose.</p>
<h3>Behavioral Remarketing</h3>
<p>Xtreme Bucket List uses remarketing services to advertise on third party websites to you after you visited our Service. We and our third-party vendors use cookies to inform, optimize and serve ads based on your past visits to our Service.</p>
<h3>Twitter</h3>
<p>Twitter remarketing service is provided by Twitter Inc.</p>
<p>You can opt-out from Twitter's interest-based ads by following their instructions: https://support.twitter.com/articles/20170405</p>
<p>You can learn more about the privacy practices and policies of Twitter by visiting their Privacy Policy page: https://twitter.com/privacy</p>
<h3>Facebook</h3>
<p>Facebook remarketing service is provided by Facebook Inc.</p>
<p>You can learn more about interest-based advertising from Facebook by visiting this page: https://www.facebook.com/help/164968693837950</p>
<p>To opt-out from Facebook's interest-based ads follow these instructions from Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/help/568137493302217</p>
<p>Facebook adheres to the Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising established by the Digital Advertising Alliance. You can also opt-out from Facebook and other participating companies through the Digital Advertising Alliance in the USA http://www.aboutads.info/choices/, the Digital Advertising Alliance of Canada in Canada http://youradchoices.ca/ or the European Interactive Digital Advertising Alliance in Europe http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/, or opt-out using your mobile device settings.</p>
<p>For more information on the privacy practices of Facebook, please visit Facebook's Data Policy: https://www.facebook.com/privacy/explanation</p>
<h3>Pinterest</h3>
<p>Pinterest remarketing service is provided by Pinterest Inc.</p>
<p>You can opt-out from Pinterest's interest-based ads by enabling the "Do Not Track" functionality of your web browser or by following Pinterest instructions: http://help.pinterest.com/en/articles/personalization-and-data</p>
<p>You can learn more about the privacy practices and policies of Pinterest by visiting their Privacy Policy page: https://about.pinterest.com/en/privacy-policy</p>
<h3>Payments</h3>
<p>We may provide paid products and/or services within the Service. In that case, we use third-party services for payment processing (e.g. payment processors).</p>
<p>We will not store or collect your payment card details. That information is provided directly to our third-party payment processors whose use of your personal information is governed by their Privacy Policy. These payment processors adhere to the standards set by PCI-DSS as managed by the PCI Security Standards Council, which is a joint effort of brands like Visa, Mastercard, American Express and Discover. PCI-DSS requirements help ensure the secure handling of payment information.</p>
<p>The payment processors we work with are:</p>
<h3>Apple Store In-App Payments</h3>
<p>Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at https://www.apple.com/legal/privacy/en-ww/</p>
<h3>Google Play In-App Payments</p>
<p>Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/</p>
<h3>Links To Other Sites</h3>
<p>Our Service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party's site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit.</p>
<p>We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services.</p>
<h3>Children's Privacy</h3>
<p>Our Service does not address anyone under the age of 13 ("Children").</p>
<p>We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your Children has provided us with Personal Data, please contact us. If we become aware that we have collected Personal Data from children without verification of parental consent, we take steps to remove that information from our servers.</p>
<h3>Changes To This Privacy Policy</h3>
<p>We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page.</p>
<p>We will let you know via email and/or a prominent notice on our Service, prior to the change becoming effective and update the "effective date" at the top of this Privacy Policy.</p>
<p>You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.</p>
<h3>Contact Us</h3>
<p>If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us:</p>
<p>•	By email: mattmackay@safe-consent.com</p>
        ]]>
    "</string>
    <string name="privacy_sumary">"
        <![CDATA[
<p>Xtreme Bucket List ("us", "we", or "our") operates the www.safe-consent.com website and the Xtreme Bucket List mobile application (the "Service").</p>
<p>This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of personal data when you use our Service and the choices you have associated with that data.</p>
<p>We use your data to provide and improve the Service. By using the Service, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions.</p>
        ]]>
    "</string>
    <string name="terms_sumary">"
        <![CDATA[
<p>Please read these Terms and Conditions ("Terms", "Terms and Conditions") carefully before using the www.safe-consent.com website and the Xtreme Bucket List mobile application (together, or individually, the "Service") operated by Xtreme Bucket List ("us", "we", or "our").</p>
<p>Your access to and use of the Service is conditioned upon your acceptance of and compliance with these Terms. These Terms apply to all visitors, users and others who wish to access or use the Service.</p>
<p>By accessing or using the Service you agree to be bound by these Terms. If you disagree with any part of the terms then you do not have permission to access the Service.</p>
        ]]>
    "</string>
    <string name="terms">"
        <![CDATA[
<h1>Terms and Conditions</h1>


<p>Last updated: May 30, 2018</p>


<p>Please read these Terms and Conditions ("Terms", "Terms and Conditions") carefully before using the www.XtremeBucketList.com website and the Xtreme Bucket List mobile application (together, or individually, the "Service") operated by Xtreme Bucket List ("us", "we", or "our").</p>

<p>Your access to and use of the Service is conditioned upon your acceptance of and compliance with these Terms. These Terms apply to all visitors, users and others who wish to access or use the Service.</p>

<p>By accessing or using the Service you agree to be bound by these Terms. If you disagree with any part of the terms then you do not have permission to access the Service.</p>














<h2>Intellectual Property</h2>

<p>The Service and its original content, features and functionality are and will remain the exclusive property of Xtreme Bucket List and its licensors. The Service is protected by copyright, trademark, and other laws of both the United States and foreign countries. Our trademarks and trade dress may not be used in connection with any product or service without the prior written consent of Xtreme Bucket List.</p>


<h2>Links To Other Web Sites</h2>

<p>Our Service may contain links to third party web sites or services that are not owned or controlled by Xtreme Bucket List</p>

<p>Xtreme Bucket List has no control over, and assumes no responsibility for the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third party web sites or services. We do not warrant the offerings of any of these entities/individuals or their websites.</p>

<p>You acknowledge and agree that Xtreme Bucket List shall not be responsible or liable, directly or indirectly, for any damage or loss caused or alleged to be caused by or in connection with use of or reliance on any such content, goods or services available on or through any such third party web sites or services.</p>

<p>We strongly advise you to read the terms and conditions and privacy policies of any third party web sites or services that you visit.</p>


<h2>Termination</h2>

<p>We may terminate or suspend your access to the Service immediately, without prior notice or liability, under our sole discretion, for any reason whatsoever and without limitation, including but not limited to a breach of the Terms.</p>

<p>All provisions of the Terms which by their nature should survive termination shall survive termination, including, without limitation, ownership provisions, warranty disclaimers, indemnity and limitations of liability.</p>


<h2>Indemnification</h2>

<p>You agree to defend, indemnify and hold harmless Xtreme Bucket List and its licensee and licensors, and their employees, contractors, agents, officers and directors, from and against any and all claims, damages, obligations, losses, liabilities, costs or debt, and expenses (including but not limited to attorney's fees), resulting from or arising out of a) your use and access of the Service, or b) a breach of these Terms.</p>



<h2>Limitation Of Liability</h2>

<p>In no event shall Xtreme Bucket List, nor its directors, employees, partners, agents, suppliers, or affiliates, be liable for any indirect, incidental, special, consequential or punitive damages, including without limitation, loss of profits, data, use, goodwill, or other intangible losses, resulting from (i) your access to or use of or inability to access or use the Service; (ii) any conduct or content of any third party on the Service; (iii) any content obtained from the Service; and (iv) unauthorized access, use or alteration of your transmissions or content, whether based on warranty, contract, tort (including negligence) or any other legal theory, whether or not we have been informed of the possibility of such damage, and even if a remedy set forth herein is found to have failed of its essential purpose.</p>


<h2>Disclaimer</h2>

<p>Your use of the Service is at your sole risk. The Service is provided on an "AS IS" and "AS AVAILABLE" basis. The Service is provided without warranties of any kind, whether express or implied, including, but not limited to, implied warranties of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose, non-infringement or course of performance.</p>

<p>Xtreme Bucket List its subsidiaries, affiliates, and its licensors do not warrant that a) the Service will function uninterrupted, secure or available at any particular time or location; b) any errors or defects will be corrected; c) the Service is free of viruses or other harmful components; or d) the results of using the Service will meet your requirements.</p>


<h2>Exclusions</h2>

<p>Some jurisdictions do not allow the exclusion of certain warranties or the exclusion or limitation of liability for consequential or incidental damages, so the limitations above may not apply to you.</p>



<h2>Governing Law</h2>

<p>These Terms shall be governed and construed in accordance with the laws of New York, United States, without regard to its conflict of law provisions.</p>

<p>Our failure to enforce any right or provision of these Terms will not be considered a waiver of those rights. If any provision of these Terms is held to be invalid or unenforceable by a court, the remaining provisions of these Terms will remain in effect. These Terms constitute the entire agreement between us regarding our Service, and supersede and replace any prior agreements we might have had between us regarding the Service.</p>


<h2>Changes</h2>

<p>We reserve the right, at our sole discretion, to modify or replace these Terms at any time. If a revision is material we will provide at least 30 days notice prior to any new terms taking effect. What constitutes a material change will be determined at our sole discretion.</p>

<p>By continuing to access or use our Service after any revisions become effective, you agree to be bound by the revised terms. If you do not agree to the new terms, you are no longer authorized to use the Service.</p>


<h2>Contact Us</h2>

<p>If you have any questions about these Terms, please contact us.</p>
        ]]>
    "</string>
</resources>
